to people in my chat.
How about you say sorry for once? How
about you fix your [__] How about
with the sensitivity?
What? What?
Test. Hello.
What's the problem?
Um,
is it is it working?
Okay. So anyways,
you should apologize why you're here.
Yeah, but s you should apologize. Susie
should apologize cuz I want to ban you.
What you've done is that you sit here
and you leech on me and you give no
thanks to the things that you're given
and you've been mean to me. You're a
[__] sick stalker and you're sadistic
and I want I want to ban you. I want to
leave you out of my life. Why are you
talking with my people here? You don't
say sorry. You're not doing anything for
me. What are you doing in my life? Get
the [__] out of here. What are you
doing? Say sorry, you piece of [__] I
hate you.
Okay, I'm just going to ban you from my
channel.
I'm glad that you get benefits from my
channel, but you're a sick stalker
and you owe me an apology, if not a
billion apologies.
stalking me and talking [__] behind my
back.
dishonest.
Why? Why are you here?
You you don't get to be a part of my
life in that way. Don't [__] leech
your way into my life and sit here in my
chat and think everything is okay. You
have something to apologize for, don't
you?
What have you been doing the past 40
days, huh,
Susy?
What have you been doing? Because it's
not something honest.
You've been mistreating me. You've been
exploiting me. You've been treating me
in a wrong way. And last time we spoke,
you were there exploiting me and
treating me in the wrong way.
So, what are you doing here? Why are you
talking to people in my chat?
How about you say sorry for once? How
about you fix your [__] How about
How about you repent for your [__] How
about you guys fix the [__] that you
ruined my life for in the past?
You don't think it it hurt me the things
that that you said when you were sitting
with TXT and Metalorian when you were
talking [__] about my father and my
family and my life after you deplatform
me and ruined my life. You don't think
that I feel hurt about that? You think
you you just walk all over my life? You
piece of [__] You're really piece of
[__] You should be ashamed of yourself.
You piece of [__] I hate you. I hate
you. Get out of my life. You [__]
[__]
Skank
Piece of [__] That's what you are.
And you know it.
You know it.
Oh, you tried to be nice. No, you
haven't.
You talk behind my back. You're
dishonest. You're lying. Piece of [__]
It's not a text for no no reason.
You were there when you deplatform me
with those other people.
You were there. You were right there
when you deplatform me with those other
people. You sit and scheme with THOSE
PEOPLE. YOU DIRTY [__] YOU PIECE OF
[__]
You should be ashamed of yourself.
You're lying to me now.
You were. You were. Okay. You were not
there. Okay. You know you're lying to
me. Lying sack of [__]
What's wrong with that?
>> What's wrong?
>> Yep.
>> No, you wouldn't.
>> Okay.
Just a moment.
>> Can never be a better place because so
busy making it.
>> You don't make it a better place.
>> Posted 6 days ago. Are you going to lie
about it now?
Are you going to lie about it now? Are
you going to lie about it now that I
caught you online saying the [__] that
you did when you guys were deplatforming
me and talking behind my back and
scheming against me and plotting to ruin
my life? You [__] [__] You scaggy
piece of [__] Go.
You are a shameless piece of [__]
You're lying to me right now.
You're lying in front of everybody to MY
FACE. YOU [__] PIECE OF [__]
I had enough of you. I had enough of you
and the people you you you belong
somewhere filthy.
>> You make it a worse place. You know
>> what
>> are you going to lie about? You stalked
me. You stalk me. YOU OBSESSIVELY stalk
me. You [__]
You going to say that's not you? Are you
going to say that's not you in this
clip? attention.
>> So because
>> do not kick us to
>> your live.
>> I didn't invite you here, did I?
>> Yeah, but but you do not kick us to an
invite.
>> Lying sack of [__]
Lacking lying sack of [__] Lying sack
of [__] You don't belong in my life.
Get out of my life. Like, why do you
keep stalking me? You sick piece of
[__]
How many times have I told you to get
out of my life, Susie? You can't even
apologize. You're even lying straight to
my face. You sack of [__] You piece of
[__] Get the [__] out of my life.
Why do you continue to do the same
thing? Why do you follow me around if
you can't do it in the right way? Why do
you disrespect me in that way? Do you
want me to come to your address and find
you and take care of you personally?
Because I will. I will find you and I
will come to your address. I will tell
you what's wrong with you.
Do you want me to do that? Because I'm
getting really [__] sick of you,
Susy. It's been 6 years and you're
stalking me every [__] day. Do you
want ME TO RETURN THE FAVOR?
NO. You have nothing to say sorry for,
right? You have nothing to apologize
for. Not even if we're lying in this
conversation and being dishonest. Piece
of [__] A stalking sack of [__]
A subhuman piece of [__] GET THE [__]
OUT OF MY LIFE.
LEAVE.
That's it. Get the [__] out,
you sack of [__]
And I'm going to report you like
whatever. Dude, you are
Get out. Get out. Get out. Leave me
alone. Get the [__] out. Okay.
Yeah. Thank you.
You guys like you just don't get it.
Yeah,
thank you for standing with me because
it's really sickening because you ruin
every year of my life and it's never
ending and so you got to get the [__]
out of my life because it's you you
leave me alone. Just leave me alone. If
you can't be right to me, just leave me
alone. You really shouldn't [__]
engage with me if you're going to ruin
my life. You really belong in jail.
AND THAT'S IT. LEAVE ME ALONE.
SO, I'm in distress and I want you to
leave me alone. I want I want you to
like just leave me alone. Like these
people, do they not get it?
I have said it like a billion times and
it makes me crazy and I don't think it's
healthy for my mental health and I don't
think that it's good for your life
either doing crimes against me. So stop
stalking me you [__] sick pieces of
[__] Get the [__] out of my life. Leave
me alone and do something else with your
life for once in the past six years. GET
THE [__] OUT of my life if you cannot if
you can't have my respect. If you can't
treat me properly, get the [__] out.
Leave